(Empire State Of Mind by
Jay Z ft. Alicia Keys)
♪ Yeah I'm out that Brooklyn
now I'm down in Tribeca ♪
♪ Right next to De Niro
but I'll be hood forever ♪
♪ I'm the new Sinatra and
since I made it here ♪
♪ I can make it anywhere yeah
they love me everywhere ♪
♪ I used to cop in Harlem ♪
♪ Hola my Dominicanos ♪
♪ Right there up on Broadway ♪
♪ Brought me back to that McDonald's ♪
♪ Took it to my stash
spot 560 State Street ♪
♪ Catch me in the kitchen like
a Simmons whipping pastry ♪
♪ Cruising down 8th
Street off-white Lexus ♪
♪ Driving so slow but BK is from Texas ♪
♪ Me I'm out that Bed-Stuy
home of that boy Biggie ♪
♪ Now I live on Billboard and
I brought my boys with me ♪
♪ Say what up to Ty Ty
still sipping Mai Tais ♪
♪ Sitting courtside Knicks
and Nets give me high fives ♪
♪ I be spiked out I could trip a referee ♪
♪ Tell by my attitude that
I'm most definitely from ♪
♪ In New York ♪
♪ Concrete jungle where
dreams are made of ♪
♪ There's nothing you can't do ♪
♪ Now you're in New York ♪
♪ These streets will
make you feel brand-new ♪
♪ Big lights will inspire you ♪
♪ Let's hear it for New York ♪
♪ New York New York ♪
♪ Catch me at the X with
OG at a Yankee game ♪
♪ I made the Yankee hat more
famous than a Yankee can ♪
♪ You should know I bleed blue
but I ain't a Crip though ♪
♪ But I got a gang of walking
with my clique though ♪
♪ Welcome to the melting pot ♪
♪ Corners where we're selling ♪
♪ Africa Bambaataa home of the hip-hop ♪
♪ Yellow cab gypsy cab
dollar cab holler back ♪
♪ For foreigners it ain't fair ♪
♪ They act like they forgot how to add ♪
♪ Eight million stories
out there in the naked ♪
♪ City it's a pity half
of y'all won't make it ♪
♪ Me I gotta plug Special
Ed I Got It Made ♪
♪ If Jeezy's paying LeBron
I'm paying Dwyane Wade ♪
♪ Three dice cee-lo three-card Marley ♪
♪ Labor Day Parade rest
in peace Bob Marley ♪
♪ Statue of Liberty long
live the World Trade ♪
♪ Long live the king yo ♪
♪ I'm from the Empire State that's ♪
♪ In New York ♪
♪ Concrete jungle where
dreams are made of ♪
♪ There's nothing you can't do ♪
♪ Now you're in New York ♪
♪ These streets will
make you feel brand-new ♪
♪ Big lights will inspire you ♪
♪ Let's hear it for New York ♪
♪ New York New York ♪
♪ Lights is blinding girls need blinders ♪
♪ So they can step out of
bounds quick the side lines is ♪
♪ Lined with casualties
who sip the life casually ♪
♪ Then gradually become worse ♪
♪ Don't bite the apple Eve ♪
♪ Caught up in the in-crowd
now you're in-style ♪
♪ Into the winter gets cold
en vogue with your skin out ♪
♪ City of sin is a pity on a whim ♪
♪ Good girls gone bad the
city's filled with them ♪
♪ Mami took a bus trip
now she got her bust out ♪
♪ Everybody ride her
just like a bus route ♪
♪ Hail Mary to the city you're a virgin ♪
♪ And Jesus can't save you life
starts when the church end ♪
♪ Came here for school
graduated to the high life ♪
♪ Ball players rap stars
addicted to the limelight ♪
♪ MDMA got you feeling like a champion ♪
♪ The city never sleeps
better slip you're a Ambien ♪
♪ In New York ♪
♪ Concrete jungle where
dreams are made of ♪
♪ There's nothing you can't do ♪
♪ Now you're in New York ♪
♪ These streets will
make you feel brand-new ♪
♪ Big lights will inspire you ♪
♪ Let's hear it for New York ♪
♪ New York New York ♪
♪ One hand in the air for the big city ♪
♪ Street lights big dreams
all looking pretty ♪
♪ No place in the world
that could compare ♪
♪ Put your lighters in
the air everybody say ♪
♪ Yeah yeah ♪
♪ In New York ♪
♪ Concrete jungle where
dreams are made of ♪
♪ There's nothing you can't do ♪
♪ Now you're in New York ♪
♪ These streets will
make you feel brand-new ♪
♪ Big lights will inspire you ♪
♪ Let's hear it for New York ♪
♪ New York New York ♪